Problem Statements for Polyhacks 1.0 

1)Develop web/app that connects 
patients  with NGO & Government  Agencies & others providing financial aids for certain diseases. That platform should allow users for the resources such as speciality hospitals offering various schemes and surgeons.

2)Develop a web/mobile platform that connects job seekers with skill development resources, such as online courses, tutorials, and mentorship programs. The platform should allow users to search for resources based on their skills and career goals, track their progress, and connect with other learners and experts in their field.

3)Design a web/mobile platform that connects local volunteer organizations with individuals looking to donate their time and skills to good causes.

4)Design a virtual wardrobe website/mobile app that allows users to upload pictures of their clothes, create outfits, and plan their outfits for the week.